http://www.ctstool.com/content/page/privacy-policy

My Account
Shopping Cart (0)
Track Your Order
Sign In
Register Now
CALL NOW :
Password
Forgot?
- Create Account
- Forgot Password?
Hardware
Please register to enjoy the full benefits of our services,
including our assistance in locating the products you require.
Item #
(MFG# {| product.ManufacturerNo_s |})
Privacy Policy
CMT is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the CMT Website and governs data collection and usage. By using the CMT website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
CMT collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. CMT also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by CMT. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by CMT for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the CMT Website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through CMT public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: CMT does not read any of your private online communications.
CMT encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from CMT so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. CMT is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the CMT and CMT family of Websites.
Use of your Personal Information
CMT collects and uses your personal information to operate the CMT Website and deliver the services you have requested. CMT also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from CMT and its affiliates. CMT may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
CMT does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. CMT may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (email, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, CMT may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to CMT, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
CMT does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
CMT keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within CMT, in order to determine what CMT services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within CMT to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
CMT Websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on CMT or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of CMT; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of CMT, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The CMT Website use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a webpage server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize CMT pages, or register with CMT site or services, a cookie helps CMT to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same CMT website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the CMT features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the CMT services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
CMT secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. CMT secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
CMT will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. CMT encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how CMT is protecting your information.
Contact Information
CMT welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that CMT has not adhered to this Statement, please contact CMT at info@cmtindustrial.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
gfhfg
Print Page
Can't Find The Tool You Need?
Request a Tool
Ask an Expert
Contact Your CMT Rep
Request a Consultaion
Newsletter Signup
Use Our Bulk Order Pad
What Our Customers Say
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, postea insolens quo te, per mazim nemore molestie no, putent oblique qualisque in cum. In case error quidam nec. Quo posse nullam conceptam in,
See More Testimonials
Supply Chain Solutions
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, postea insolens quo te, per mazim nemore molestie no, putent oblique qualisque in cum. In case error quidam nec. Quo posse nullam conceptam in,
Improve Your Supply Chain
We Help You Succeed Case Study Title Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, postea insolens quo te, per mazim nemore molestie no, putent oblique qualisque in cum. In case error quidam nec. Quo posse nullam concepta Article Title Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, postea insolens quo te, per mazim nemore molestie no, putent oblique qualisque in cum. In case error quidam nec. Quo posse nullam concepta
<< Close Catalog
CMT Headquarters
300 Industrial Drive
Greenville, SC 29607
Phone: 864-271-2871
Toll Free: 800-868-4268
Fax: 864-271-3237
CMT
@ 1994 - 2014, company name, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
